<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>🔅 Caustics</title>
      <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on 🔅 Caustics</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Shader Properties</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/how-to-guides/shader-properties</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/how-to-guides/shader-properties</guid>
    <description>How to use this asset. This asset comes with a nice and clean material editor to edit the properties of the caustics. This editor will simply show up in the material section in the inspector if you have the caustics volume selected.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 11:10:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Caustics Volume</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/how-to-guides/caustics-volume</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/how-to-guides/caustics-volume</guid>
    <description>How to place caustics. Caustics may be positioned using caustics volumes. These volumes are cubes that may be translated, rotated and scaled. Caustics will show up wherever the volume intersects with existing scene geometry.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 11:09:54 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Changelog</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/changelog</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/changelog</guid>
    <description>All notable changes to this package will be documented in this file. The format is based on Keep a Changelog, and this project adheres to Semantic Versioning.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 10:46:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Contact</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/contact</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/contact</guid>
    <description>How to get in touch. Hi! I am Alexander, the developer of Water Caustics for URP. You can reach me in the following ways: Discord: discord.com/invite/cFfQGzQdPn Twitter: @alexanderameye Email: alexanderameye@gmail.com Website: ameye.dev.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:12:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Compatibility</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/compatibility</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/compatibility</guid>
    <description>Check if Linework will work in your project. Compatibility Linework is compatible with Unity 6 and the Universal Render Pipeline. Other combinations are not supported.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:12:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>About Caustics</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/about-caustics</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/about-caustics</guid>
    <description>Thanks for your interest in Water Caustics for URP! You have already downloaded Water Caustics for URP and want to get started? Read the Getting Started section ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:12:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>About Linework</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/</guid>
    <description>Thanks for your interest in Linework! If you have already installed Linework and you want to get started? Read the Getting Started section. Linework for Unity - A Practical Toolkit for Rendering Outlines With Linework you can render high-quality outlines in Unity.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:12:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Getting Started</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/getting-started</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/getting-started</guid>
    <description>How to get started using Water Caustics for URP. Before using Water Caustics for URP, review the following important notes. License Agreement The source code included with this asset can be freely modified to suit your needs.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:12:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Troubleshooting and Known Limitations</title>
    <link>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/troubleshooting-and-known-limitations</link>
    <guid>https://caustics.ameye.dev/support/troubleshooting-and-known-limitations</guid>
    <description>Some frequently encountered issues and how to resolve them. Can’t find a solution to your issue here? Contact me. Known Limitations (fixes in progress) Soft/Wide Outline + MSAA Having Anti Aliasing (MSAA) enabled in the Universal Render Pipeline Asset will result in an error and the outlines will not render.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:17:30 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>